{
    "Levels": [
        {
            "level": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "problem": "HTML",
                    "solution": "HyperText Markup Language"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "problem": "CSS",
                    "solution": "Cascading Style Sheets"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "problem": "JS",
                    "solution": "JavaScript"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "problem": "JPEG",
                    "solution": "Joint Photographic Experts Group"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "problem": "PNG",
                    "solution": "Portable Network Graphics"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "problem": "Graphics Interchange Format",
                    "solution": "GIF"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "problem": "JSON",
                    "solution": "JavaScript Object Notation"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "problem": "XML",
                    "solution": "eXtensible Markup Language"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "problem": "YAML",
                    "solution": "Yet Another Markup Language"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "problem": "<ul></ul>",
                    "solution": "nečíslovaný zoznam"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "problem": "<ol></ol>",
                    "solution": "číslovaný zoznam"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "problem": "<li></li>",
                    "solution": "položky v zozname"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "level": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "problem": "WWW",
                    "solution": "World Wide Web"
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "problem": "HTTP",
                    "solution": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol"
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "problem": "HTTPS",
                    "solution": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}